Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
- Box: 59, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The British Civil Service, 1959; Publication (Box 59, Folder 10)
    Author: British Civil Service
  - Item 2: Labour relations and working conditions in Britain, 1960; Publication (Box 59, Folder 10)
    Author: Great Britain. Central Office of Information. Reference Division
  - Item 3: Health services in Britain, 1960; Publication (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Box: 59, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: British Socialism today, Publication (Box 59, Folder 11)
    Author: R.H. Tawney
- Box: 59, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Eve in overalls, Publication (Box 59, Folder 12)
    Author: Arthur Wauters
- Box: 59, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The European approach to worker-management relationships, 1973; Publication (Box 59, Folder 13)
    Author: Innis Macbeath
- Box: 59, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The staggering of holidays: report to the Minister of Labour and National Service by the Catering Wages Commission under Section 2 of the Catering Wages Act, 1943, 1945; Publication (Box 59, Folder 14)
    Author: Great Britain. Catering Wages Commission
- Box: 59, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Russia and the Daily Worker, Publication (Box 59, Folder 15)
    Author: William Rust
  - Item 2: The General Council & the general strike: an analysis of the General Council's report on the strike, 1926; Publication (Box 59, Folder 15)
    Author: A.J.Bennet
  - Item 3: When the whistle blows: economics for trade unionists: a series of lunch hour talks, 1954; Publication (Box 59, Folder 15)
    Author: Ted Ainley
- Box: 59, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: How best to do away with the sweating system, 1892; Publication (Box 59, Folder 16)
    Author: Beatrice Potter
- Box: 59, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Keep the unions free: a statement on the Rookes v. Barnard case, 1964; Publication (Box 59, Folder 17)
    Author: Draughtsmen's and Allied Technicians' Associaiton (Great Britain)
- Box: 59, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Forced labour under communism: twenty questions and answers, 1959; Publication (Box 59, Folder 18)
- Box: 59, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Reports on subjects of general and commercial interest: Italy: report on the condition of labour in Italy, 1891; Publication (Box 59, Folder 19)
    Author: Great Britain. Foreign Office
- Box: 59, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Report and statement of accounts of the Amalgamated Society of Wire Drawers and Kindred Workers, 1932; Publication (Box 59, Folder 20)
    Author: Amalgamated Society of Wire Drawers and Kindred Workers
- Box: 59, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Secretary General's Report, 1979; Publication (Box 59, Folder 21)
    Author: Singapore National Trades Union Congress
    Notes: 3rd Triennial
  - Item 2: Devan, Nation Builder, People's President, 1981; Publication (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: NTUC Ordinary Delegates Conference, 1992; Publication (Box 59, Folder 21)
- Box: 59, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: May Dan annual, 1982; Publication (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: NTUC ordinary delegates' conference, 1982; Publication (Box 59, Folder 22)
- Box: 59, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Empact, 1979; Publication (Box 59, Folder 23)
    Author: South Africa. Bureau of International Labour Affairs
- Box: 59, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Official South African trade unions directory and industrial relations handbook, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 24)
- Box: 59, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Employee investment funds, 1984; Publication (Box 59, Folder 25)
    Author: Sweden. Finansdepartementet
  - Item 2: The trade unions in figures, 1990; Publication (Box 59, Folder 25)
    Author: Landsorganisationen i Sverige
  - Item 3: The labour movement and employee investment funds: history, recommendations and commentary, 1982; Publication (Box 59, Folder 25)
- Box: 59, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Mer makt at de anstallda, Publication (Box 59, Folder 26)
    Language: Swedish.
  - Item 2: Stadgar for Tjanstemannens Centralorganisation, Publication (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Detta ar TCO, Publication (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Det fackliga bistandet, Publication (Box 59, Folder 26)
- Box: 59, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1971; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
    Author: LO
  - Item 2: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1971; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
    Notes: no.1. Photocopy
  - Item 3: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1970; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1970; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1970; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1969; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 10: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 13: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 14: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 15: Series III, Informaiton to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 16: Series III, Information to foreign countries, 1968; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 17: Nyhetsbrev, 2001; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 18: The trade unions in figures, 1990; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 19: The trade union movement and the multinationals: report presented to the 1976 Congress of the Swedish Trade Union Confederation: summary, 1977; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 20: This how the trade unions work together with Verdandi, 1986; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Item 21: Working environment agreement: [agreement regarding general rules for working environment activities in industry ...], 1979; Publication (Box 59, Folder 27)
    Author: Svenska arbetsgivareforeningen; Arbetarskyddsnamnden
- Box: 59, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The trade union movement and the social policy, 1977; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: I samarbeid og strid, 1935-1995 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 3: Rettferdighet: et prinsipielt handlingsprogram for Landsorganisasjonen I Norge, 1997-2001 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 4: Agreement on rationalization between the Swedish Employers' Confederation (SAF) and the Swedish Confederation of Trade Unions (LO), signed June 1, 1972, 1974; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
    Author: Svenska arbetsgivareforeningen
  - Item 5: Development of labour peace in Sweden, 1971; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 6: The Volvo Kalmar plant, 1976; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
    Author: Stefan Aguren
  - Item 7: Det fackliga bistandet, 1991/92; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 8: This is LO, 1996; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 9: LO's health project, 1988; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 10: Migrant workers and the trade union movement: LOs programme of action for migrant workers., 1980; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Item 11: Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1970; Publication (Box 59, Folder 28)
- Box: 59, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: News of the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1979; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: 1980s wage negotiations resulted in the biggest industrial conflict ever experienced in Sweden, Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Co-determination in Sweden: an up to date analysis of developments and the reforms implemented in the 70s, 1979; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 4: Research for work and democracy, 1980; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: This is how we work for equality between men and women in working life and in the trade unions: some advice on methods, 1980; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 6: Research: a question for the trade union movement, 1979; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 7: Trade unions and occupational health services, 1986; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 8: The LO's programme of action on asbestos 1985, Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: New initiatives: some ideas for activities together with young unemployed people, 1987; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 10: Working environment research, 1983; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: Working environment research, 1983; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Item 12: Trade union education in Sweden today, 1979; Publication (Box 59, Folder 29)
- Box: 59, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Democratization and reorganization, Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
    Author: Erik Karlsson
  - Item 2: Occupational safety and health in Sweden, Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
    Author: Sven Kvarnstrom
  - Item 3: The Act relating to allocation to work environment fund, Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Three-year agreement reached between SAF and LO, 1971; Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Research for work and democracy, 1980; Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: Research for work and democracy, 1980; Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Research for work and democracy, 1980; Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: Trade union social work, 1981; Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: Co-determination through collective agreements and legislation, 1982; Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Working hours and employment: views of the Swedish Trade Union Confederation (LO), 1983; Publication (Box 59, Folder 30)
- Box: 60, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: This is how we work for equality between men and women in working life and in the trade unions, 1980; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Trade union programme of action against asbestos, Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: This is how an agreement comes into being, 1978; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1987; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Comments by the Swedish Central Organization of Salaried Employees concerning the "World Plan of Action" approved by the UN International Women's Conference and the Declaration and plan of action adopted by the 1975 ILO conference concerning equal opport, 1976; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Author: Tjanstemannens centralorganisation
  - Item 6: Mental and social hazards to health in the working environment, 1980; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Trade unions and the working environment, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Documentation: English, Deutsch, Espanol, Francais, 1986; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Language: English; German; Spanish; French.
  - Item 9: Documentation: English, Deutsch, Espanol, Francais, 1986; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: LO Sweden, Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: LO's role in the framing and implementation of school and educational policy reforms in Sweden, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Box: 60, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Mental and social hazards to health in the working environment, 1980; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Documentation: English, Deutsch, Espanol, Francais, 1986; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Trade union perspectives on European integration, 1990; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: LO and family policy, 1987; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The medical, psychological and social consequences of the scheduling of working hours, 1978; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: 3 years with employee investment funds, 1988; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Author: Stig Carlsson
  - Item 7: Young people's welfare, 1990; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Some important questions for the 1986 LO congress: a summary, Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: LO News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1988; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Notes: no. 2
  - Item 10: LO News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1988; Publication (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Box: 60, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: LO News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1986; Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: LO News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1986; Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Notes: no. 3
  - Item 3: LO News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1987; Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: LO News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1988; Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: LO News from the Swedish Trade Union Confederation, 1992; Publication (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Box: 60, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Worklife Research, 1988; Publication (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Box: 60, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: SAC Statistik, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Studie stod I tio lander, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Vaxel verkan, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Ratta upp arbetsratten, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: SACO, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Facts about SACO, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Ett battre forsakrings system, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Lon efter varde, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Verige pa efterkalken, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Lonen en drivkraft I bra verksamhet, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Ag alet, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Studier till vilket pris?, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Sverige behover fler kunskaps- entreprenorer, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: En politik for flera jobb, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 15: Samarbetsavtal TCO SACO, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: SACO, the Swedish Confederation of Professional Associations, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Station, Publication (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Box: 60, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The SAF year 1993, Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Business payroll overheasds, 1994, Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The first-line manager, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Author: Lars Lindestad
  - Item 4: Documentation, 1978; Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Going for growth, Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Author: Swedish Employers Confederation
  - Item 6: The Prospects for Supervisory Development, Publication (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Notes: ad. For book
- Box: 60, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Swedish Engineering Employers' Association and the Swedish Union of Clerical and Technical Employees in Industry, the Swedish Foremen's and Supervisors' Association, the Swedish Association of Graduate Engineers concerning general co, 1970; Publication (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Box: 60, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: This is TCO, Publication (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Box: 60, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Organization of the Occupational Health Service at Gotaverken, Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Agreement concerning time and motion studies concluded by Swedish Employers' Confederation and Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions, 1959; Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Agreements regarding works councils between the Swedish Employers' Confederation and the Confederation of Swedish Trade Unions and between the Swedish Employers' Confederation and the Central Organization of Salaried Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Agreement on rationalization between the Swedish Employers' Confederation (SAF) and the Swedish Confederation of Trade Unions (LO), signed June 1, 1972, 1974; Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Agreements regarding works councils; Agreement on the promotion of collaboration between management and employees; Statement on training, 1967; Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Industrial safety and company health services, 1968; Publication (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Box: 60, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Perspective on labour conditions in Sweden, 1962; Publication (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Autonomous groups and payment by result, 1973; Publication (Box 60, Folder 10)
    Author: Hans Lindestad
- Box: 60, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Toward greater job insurance, 1974; Publication (Box 60, Folder 11)
    Author: Roger Nye Choate
- Box: 60, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A reform of Swedish Labour Legislation, 1972; Publication (Box 60, Folder 12)
    Author: Ministry of Labour and Housing (Sweden)
- Box: 60, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Des societes mutuelles de consommation, 1858; Publication (Box 60, Folder 13)
    Author: Edouard Raoux
  - Item 2: Agreement of 19th July 1937/1954, Publication (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: International Metalworkers' Federation, 1959; Publication (Box 60, Folder 13)
    Notes: no. 1974
- Box: 60, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: 77me Rapport annuel du comite et du conseil, 1982; Publication (Box 60, Folder 14)
    Author: Association patronale suisse des constructeurs de machines
- Box: 60, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Statuten des schweizerischen gewerkschafts bundes, Publication (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Statuten des schweizerischen gewerkschafts bundes, Publication (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Box: 60, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Das Berufsbildungs- konzept des SGB, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Formatiomn professionnelle: le modele USS, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Nouvelles techniques et protection des donnees dans l'entreprise, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Nouvelles techniques et protection des donnees dans l'entreprise, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Securite et sante au travail, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Amiante et sante au travail, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Programme de travail de l' union syndicale suisse, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
    Author: Schweizerischen Gewerkschaftsbund
  - Item 8: Programme de travail de l' union syndicale suisse, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Box: 60, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Kommentar zum gesamtarbeitsvertrag, Publication (Box 60, Folder 17)
    Author: Schriftenreihe des Schweizerischen Gewerkschaftsbndes
  - Item 2: Asbest und gesundheit am arbeitsplatz, Publication (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Neue techniken und deatenschutz im betrieb, Publication (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Sicherheit und gesundheit am arbeitsplatz, Publication (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Box: 60, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Equal pay and job evaluation, Publication (Box 60, Folder 18)
    Author: General and Municipal Workers Union
  - Item 2: GMW: Shop Steward's handbook, Publication (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Rule book: incorporating amendments adopted by Congress '90, Publication (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Box: 60, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Report on conferences between employers, operatives and inspectors concerning fencing of machinery, first aid and and other safeguards in cotton weaving factories, 1929; Publication (Box 60, Folder 19)
    Author: Eliot F. May
  - Item 2: Report on conferences between employers, operatives and inspectors concerning fencing of machinery, prevention of accidents, first aid and temperature in cotton spinning mills, 1929; Publication (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Box: 60, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The right to be recognised, 1978; Publication (Box 60, Folder 20)
    Author: Incomes Data Services
- Box: 60, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Labour and industrial peace, 1924; Publication (Box 60, Folder 21)
    Author: Thomas Shaw
- Box: 60, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The war and the workers, 1941; Publication (Box 60, Folder 22)
    Author: Ernest Bevin
- Box: 60, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Unity: will organized labor's dream come true?, 1955; Publication (Box 60, Folder 23)
    Author: William Kashtan
- Box: 60, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A worker's day under German occupation, 1942; Publication (Box 60, Folder 24)
    Author: Jim Griffiths
- Box: 60, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Cutbacks, closures & takeovers: LRD's guide to redundancy rights, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
    Author: Labour Research Department
  - Item 2: A guide to unemployment benefit, 1959; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Bosses' freedoms, workers' burdens, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 4: The miners' case, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Job evaluation: the LRD guide, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Privatisation: the great sellout, 1985; Publication (Box 60, Folder 25)
- Box: 60, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Women in industry, Publication (Box 60, Folder 26)
    Author: Joan Thomson
  - Item 2: Historical background of the world labor movement, 1944; Publication (Box 60, Folder 26)
    Author: E.W. Campbell
- Box: 60, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Notts, Miners against pit closures & job losses, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Notts, Miners against pit closures & job losses, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: The Notts Striker, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
    Notes: v.1:no.1
  - Item 4: With the miners, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: With the miners, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 6: Cannock Chase Miners Staffordshire, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: The Miners' strike, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
    Author: National Union of Mineworkers
  - Item 8: Yorkshire Miner, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
    Notes: Strike issue 5
  - Item 9: Yorkshire Miner, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
    Notes: Strike issue 6
  - Item 10: The Miner, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
    Notes: Special Issue
  - Item 11: The Miner, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Great Britain: Miners and their families against pit closures, 1984; Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 13: With the miners, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
    Notes: Article
  - Item 14: We want you to win, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Item 15: Support striking British Miners, Publication (Box 60, Folder 27)